<p> <a href="https://inforiver.com/analytics-plus/">Inforiver Analytics+</a> is the fastest way to visualize your data and share insightful stories in Microsoft Power BI as a Power BI Certified Visual. Analytics+ also enables large enterprises to migrate from Tableau, Spotfire, Qlik, Domo, Cognos, SAP Lumira, or their static PowerPoint dashboards from Think-cell or Mekko Graphics and consolidate them within Microsoft Power BI. </p>
<p>The intuitive, no-code user experience (UX) helps even casual users build dashboards and storyboards in minutes, with 100+ charts, cards, and tables integrated into a single visual.</p>
<p>Inforiver Analytics+ is your one-stop visual with the best performance among all custom visuals. It can render 10x more data points compared to native Power BI (30K data points Vs 1K - 3.5K data points).<p>
<p>Inforiver Analytics+ is certified by <a href="https://www.ibcs.com/software/inforiver/">IBCS</a> and offers the most number of IBCS-certified templates, better performance, and flexibility over any other IBCS-certified software in the market.</p>
<p>View an interactive demo of Inforiver Analytics+ <a href="https://inforiver.com/demos/analytics-plus-power-bi-introduction/">here.</a></p>
<p><b>Why choose Inforiver Analytics+ as your migration companion to Power BI:</b></p>
<ol>
    <li>100+ advanced visualization options, including some of the most
        sought-after and advanced visualizations on Power BI, like:
        <ul>
            <li>20+ <a href="https://inforiver.com/demos/advanced-waterfall-charts-in-power-bi/">advanced waterfall chart</a> types - Measure-based interim, stacked,
                and dual breakdown waterfall, variance, and combination waterfalls</li>
            <li><a href="https://inforiver.com/demos/marimekko-charts-power-bi/">Marimekko chart</a> (variable width column or cascade chart) - stacking and 100% scales</li>
            <li>Radar/Polar/Spider chart</li>
            <li><a href="https://inforiver.com/demos/box-and-whisker-plot-power-bi/">Box Plot and whisker plot</a> with
                support for dynamic and pre-calculated
                quartiles</li>
            <li>12+ variations of <a href="https://inforiver.com/demos/bullet-charts-in-power-bi/">bullet and integrated
                    variance charts</a> and more</li>
            <li>Advanced combination and dual-axes charts</li>
            <li>Hierarchical treemap, sunburst chart</li>
            <li>Slope graph</li>
            <li>Arrow chart, dumbbell chart, dot plot, range plot</li>
            <li>Pie chart, Donut chart, Variable pie chart</li>
            <li>Scatter chart, Quadrant chart, Bubble chart</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
    <li><a href="https://inforiver.com/demos/storytelling-inforiver-charts/">Storytelling features</a> like Think-cell
        and Mekko Graphics
        <ul>
            <li>Dynamic Dynamic deviation (total and by level) and CAGR</li>
            <li>Annotations</li>
            <li>Series connector lines</li>
            <li>Automatic series and categorical sorting</li>
        </ul>
    </li>

    <li>Structure Pivot data for your hierarchical data on all three axes (x,y,z) like Spotfire</li>
    <li>Small Multiple &amp; Trellis for all chart types and KPI cards</li>
    <li>Split and Group Measures into Trellis panels like Tableau</li>
    <li>Integrated variance support without DAX. Available for bar, line, waterfall, bullet, and boxplot visuals</li>
    <li>Visual calculated rows and columns/Quick editing inside the visual with
        no DAX</li>
    <li>Most voted and unmet feature features requests from Power BI Idea
        place and various other BI platforms, such as:
        <ul>
            <li>Measure-driven data labels</li>
            <li>100% stacked bar with column totals</li>
            <li>Dynamic ranking support without DAX</li>
            <li>Legend interactions (Highlight, include, exclude)</li>
            <li>Stacked waterfall chart</li>
            <li>Gradient line chart</li>
            <li>Dynamic axis break</li>
            <li>Scale bands</li>
        </ul>
    </li>
    <li>Storyboarding - Rapidly build dashboards in minutes with templates
        and smart layouts</li>
</ol>
<p>More visualizations such as Swarm Plot, Parallel Coordinates, Tornado Chart, Cluster Lollipop, Progress Bar, Sankey, Stream, Map Chart, Proportion Plot, and many more chart types will be added to Analytics+ soon. You can check out our <a
        href="https://inforiver.com/blog/general/inforiver-charts-vision-roadmap/">vision and roadmap</a> here.</p>
<p>You can reach out to the Inforiver <a href="mailto:support@inforiver.com">Support team</a> for any queries.
