<p>
  <a href="https://inforiver.com/editable/">EDITable</a> provides a
  self-service platform that helps you manage reference data for your
  reporting &amp; planning applications in Power BI. It complements your Master
  Data Management (MDM) solution and offers a lightweight alternative for
  business users that supports both reference data (such as customer,
  region, and product master) and flat tables (such as price list,
  contracts, projects, and discounts).
</p>

<h2>Highlights</h2>
<ul>
  <li>Edit dimensions &amp; measures in flat tables</li>
  <li>
    Designed for business users; requires minimal help and setup from IT
  </li>
  <li>Migrate your first Excel table to EDITable in three (3) minutes</li>
  <li>
    Supports LIVE sync with data residing in Azure SQL, Databricks,
    Snowflake, Microsoft Fabric, RedShift, and Postgres
  </li>
</ul>

<h2>Features</h2>
<ul>
  <li>Bulk Insert/Edit values</li>
  <li>
    Custom approval workflows (table-level, dimension-level, and
    value-based)
  </li>
  <li>Supports Slowly Changing Dimensions (SCD) Type II</li>
  <li>Change log for enabling audit</li>
  <li>Conditional formatting</li>
  <li>Commenting &amp; collaboration</li>
  <li>Data integration with webhooks</li>
  <li>Granular user activity permissions (add/delete/edit rows)</li>
  <li>Columnar permissions (ACL)</li>
</ul>

<h2>Power Your Planning Applications Using EDITable</h2>
<p>
  EDITable ensures that you have full control over master data supporting
  your planning applications. Be it products, regions, accounts, cost
  centers, customers, employees, or salaries - you can maintain everything
  with ease to ensure the integrity of your plans and forecasts.
</p>
<p>
  EDITable makes it much easier to incorporate forward-looking master data
  that is needed for planning, especially master data that is not yet
  created in your transaction systems or data warehouses.
</p>

<h2>EDITable vs. Other Matrix Visuals with Writeback</h2>
<p>
  Discover how EDITable is different from other matrix visuals with
  writeback capabilities:
</p>
<ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Data Store:</strong> A matrix visual typically consumes data
    from Table A, and writes back data to Table B. With EDITable, the source
    &amp; destination tables are (must be) the same as you are working on
    reference data (which can used by multiple other applications).
  </li>
  <li>
    <strong>Connectivity:</strong> A matrix visual typically supports both
    Import and DirectQuery modes. EDITable can only consume DirectQuery
    (Live) connections.
  </li>
  <li>
    <strong>Data Type:</strong> A matrix visual typically allows you to
    update measures; EDITable can be used to update both dimensions &amp;
    measures.
  </li>
  <li>
    <strong>Sample Use Cases:</strong> Matrix products are best suited for
    planning and forecasting applications; EDITable works well for
    maintaining reference data and flat tables such as price lists, vendor
    lists, etc.
  </li>
  <li>
    <strong>Structure:</strong> Matrix products work well with hierarchical
    data; EDITable exclusively supports flat (non-hierarchical) tables, and
    offers support for slowly changing dimensions (SCD Type II).
  </li>
</ul>

<h2>Learn More</h2>
<ul>
  <li>
    Visit our <a href="https://inforiver.com/editable/">website</a> to learn
    more.
  </li>
  <li>
    Join our upcoming
    <a href="https://www.inforiver.com/webinars">webinars</a> / replay past
    webinars.
  </li>
  <li>
    Follow us on
    <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/editable">LinkedIn</a> and
    <a href="https://youtube.com/@inforiverbi">YouTube</a>.
  </li>
  <li>
    Post technical questions and interact with other users in the Inforiver
    community.
  </li>
  <li>
    <a href="https://editable.io/contact-us">Schedule a demo</a> with our
    sales team.
  </li>
</ul></div></div><div class="capabilities"><h3 class="c-heading-6 capabilitiesTitle">Visual capabilities</h3><div class="disclaimer"><div>When this visual is used, it</div></div><ul class="capabilitiesList"><li class="capabilitiesListItem">Can access external services or resources</li></ul></div></div>