<div class="appDetailContent"><div><h2 class="shortDescription appsource-css-527"><div>The most comprehensive matrix for Financial, Management, Variance, Paginated &amp; IBCS reporting </div></h2><div class="description"><p>Create management &amp; financial reports in minutes using Inforiver. Inforiver Matrix offers expand/collapse capability on both row and column hierarchies, row and column grouping, reordering, and more. The product supports paginated reports, IBCS variance reports, financial statements, executive scorecards, editable forecasting &amp; budgeting templates, cell-level annotations, slider-based simulations, in-cell charts, Excel-like formulae, and formatted exports to Excel / PDF. </p> 
<p>The innovative user experience is facilitated by an advanced toolbar menu and context-menu interactions. Inforiver is certified by both Microsoft and International Business Communication Standards (IBCS).</p> 
<p>This edition of Inforiver works independently in Power BI and does not require any additional backend infrastructure such as a database, server, or web service.</p>
<b>Inforiver Premium Edition Feature Highlights:</b> <br>
<b>1.  Management &amp; financial performance reports</b> 
<ul> 
<li> Spreadsheet-like cell, row, and column formatting
</li><li> Re-order and group rows and columns using click-and-drag action
</li><li> Advanced number formatting &amp; dynamic scaling
</li><li> Nested and/or filtering, Top N + others and more
</li><li> One-click IBCS templates
</li></ul> 
 
<b>2.  Paginated reports</b> 
<ul> 
<li> First-Previous-Next-Last style navigation
</li><li> Custom page, row, column, and section breaks based on categories
</li><li> Export to Excel with each category on a unique worksheet
</li><li> Advanced header and footer with images, text, charts, and KPI cards
</li>
</ul> 
  
<b>3.  Input/edit data &amp; perform visual calculations </b>  
<ul> 
<li> Edit/update data in existing cells
</li><li>Insert new rows &amp; columns that support data input &amp; formulae
</li><li>Use Excel-like intuitive formulae &amp; calculations
</li><li>70+ functions - math, logical, text, finance, statistical, and more 
</li> 
</ul> 
  
<b>4.  Planning, budgeting &amp; forecasting </b>  
<ul> 
<li>Create budgets using a blank template from scratch, or using performance data for current/prior periods 
</li><li>Spread/allocate projections entered at parent level to descendants based on weights of other measures (e.g., forecasts based on prior year data) or drivers (overhead distributed by department headcount)
</li><li>Supports both top-down and bottom-up planning and budgeting 
</li><li>Use a graphical slider to perform what-if simulations 
</li><li>Create rolling forecasts by blending actuals &amp; forecasts
</li><li>Lock/unlock specific cells, rows &amp; columns for editing
</li>  
</ul><br>  
 
<b>5.  Formatted export to Excel/PDF </b>  
<ul> 
<li>Perform formatted export of data along with font style, background, in-cell notes, footnotes, and data bars to Excel 
</li><li>Export charts, in-cell visualizations, and paginations to PDF including formatting and annotations  
</li>  
</ul><br> 

<b>6.  Other</b>  
<ul> 
<li>Spreadsheet-like pivot analysis with Excel-like table layouts 
</li><li>Nest measures above categories in columns
</li><li>50+ in-cell charts and visualizations in a single click
</li><li>Cell, row &amp; column-level notes/footnotes &amp; annotations, report summary, roll-up notes with filter/slicer context awareness
</li>  
</ul><br> 

<p> 
To know more about, visit : <a href="https://inforiver.com/">Inforiver </a>
</p>

<p>If you are looking for data writeback, scheduling &amp; collaboration capabilities in addition to all the above, try out <a href="https://appsource.microsoft.com/en-us/product/power-bi-visuals/xviz.inforiver-enterprise">Inforiver Enterprise</a>.</p></div></div><div class="capabilities"><h3 class="c-heading-6 capabilitiesTitle">Visual capabilities</h3><div class="disclaimer"><div>This visual is certified by Power BI</div><div><a href="https://aka.ms/power-bi-custom-visuals-certified" class="c-hyperlink" tabindex="0"><span>Learn more about certified Power BI visuals.</span></a></div></div></div></div>