<p>
  Introducing ValQ, the modern no-code planning solution that is very
  intuitive, interactive and for instant strategic decision making. It
  integrates seamlessly with Microsoft Power BI. ValQ has been architected and
  modernized to Unlock wide range of your planning and forecasting use cases
  with ValQ's innovative visual no-code business modelling user experience.
</p>
<ul>
  <li>
    Independent and Serverless: ValQ operates without the need for databases,
    servers, or IT support, offering a hassle-free experience.
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Analyst-Centric Design: No coding or scripting skills are required to
    build models in ValQ
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Scalable Templates: Easily scale your model using templates while keeping
    it dynamic
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Mathematical Formulae &amp; Functions: Leverage a library of spreadsheet-like
    mathematical formulae and functions to build complex planning models.
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Simple Model Management: Live data preview, error validation, bulk editing
    capabilities, advanced search, and filtering for smooth model management.
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>Notes: Perform cell-level and node-level notes.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Reporting: Generate reports in various styles with charts and export them
    to Excel/PDF.
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Generate reports of different styles with charts and export to excel/pdf
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Presentations: Interactive Presentation Mode: Present your finalized
    decisions to management with an interactive presentation mode that
    delivers a seamless experience
  </li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Simulations &amp; Analysis</strong></p>
<ul>
  <li>
    What-If Simulations: Perform what-if simulations on the fly using a
    drag-drop interface and visualize impact on outcomes instantly &amp;
    intuitively in tree as well as spreadsheet like format
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Scenario Comparisons: Create multiple scenarios and compare scenario
    outcomes in a few minutes, not hours.
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Insights and Decisions: Gain valuable insights into model performance with
    chart visuals and make quick actionable decisions using the KPI tracker.
  </li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Time-Series forecasting</strong></p>
<ul>
  <li>
    Multiple Methods: Perform time-series forecasting without external
    libraries. Choose from various methods like Linear Trend, Weighted
    Average, Moving Average, ARIMA, Single Exponential Smoothing, Holt’s
    Method, and Holt’s Winter Method.
  </li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Planning</strong></p>
<ul>
  <li>
    Plan Creation: Create plans based on recent performance, forecasting
    methods, or start from scratch with a blank template for zero-based
    budgeting
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Smart Planning Interface: Leverage an intelligent and editable table
    interface for intuitive top-down and bottom-up planning, complete with
    simple mathematical operations with scaling.
  </li>
</ul>
<ul>
  <li>
    Efficient Updates: Automatically distribute updates across planning
    hierarchies and time with spreading and allocation methods, including
    weights-based, trend-based, and driver-based, along with goal seeking.
  </li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Additional Information</strong></p>
<p>
  For downloadable demos (.pbix files):
  <a target="_blank" href="https://valq.com/demos">Demos</a>
</p>
<p>
  For pricing:
  <a target="_blank" href="https://valq.com/pricing/#certified">Pricing</a>
  (per-user and team pricing available)
</p>
<p>
  For sales enquiries: sales@valq.com For technical enquiries &amp; support:
  <a target="_blank" href="https://valq.com/support">Support Portal</a>
</p>
<p>Reach us <a href="mailto:support@valq.com">here</a></p>
<p>
  Join our online community and get all your questions answered at
  <a target="_blank" href="https://community.valq.com">Community</a>
</p>
</div></div></div><div class="capabilities"><h3 class="c-heading-6 capabilitiesTitle">Visual capabilities</h3><div class="disclaimer"><div>This visual is certified by Power BI</div><div><a href="https://aka.ms/power-bi-custom-visuals-certified" class="c-hyperlink" tabindex="0"><span>Learn more about certified Power BI visuals.</span></a></div></div></div></div>